const mathformulas = [
  { question: "Рассчитайте значение", formula: "2*8", answer: "16" },
  { question: "Рассчитайте значение", formula: "34/2", answer: "17" },
  { question: "Рассчитайте значение", formula: "3+5", answer: "8" },
  { question: "Рассчитайте значение", formula: "3*3", answer: "9" },
  { question: "Рассчитайте значение", formula: "2*5", answer: "10" },
  { question: "Рассчитайте значение", formula: "5+10", answer: "15" },
  { question: "Рассчитайте значение", formula: "22/2", answer: "11" },
  { question: "Выберите четное число: 1, 10, 25", answer: "10" },
  { question: "Выберите простое число: 4, 9, 11", answer: "11" },
  { question: "Переведите из римской в арабскую систему счисления: IV", answer: "4" }
];
export default mathformulas;
